MEGHAN SATTERLEY

meghan.satterley@gmail.com | 816-830-8572 Independence, MO 64055 | GitHub: Meghan-Satterley

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Current undergraduate student pursuing a Bachelor's of Science in Computer Science at the University of Missouri-Kansas City (2024) with knowledge of C++ and Assembly Language, building skills in Java and Python. With an eagerness to work along side experienced members to enhance professional skills. An excellent work ethic, with experience in dead-line based, fast-paced environments and a readiness to learn.

SKILLS

Time Management

Detail Oriented

Team Player

Strong Communication

Eagerness to Learn

Patience

C++

Assembly Language

HTML

JavaScript

CSS

WORK HISTORY

Senior Supervisor | Charlie's Car Wash - INDEPENDENCE, MO

11/2019 - Current

- Identified underperforming areas and implemented effective process improvements.
- Coordinated, supervised and evaluated work of subordinates and reallocated staff and resources to meet performance requirements.
- Assumed responsibility and oversight for hiring, onboarding and mentoring new staff members.
- Assessed problems and conflicts and resolved independently.

Sales Associate | Michaels Arts And Crafts - Jacksonville, Florida

02/2018 - 06/2019

Provided positive first impressions to welcome existing, new, and potential

customers.

- Maintained calm demeanor and professionally managed issues in busy, highstress situations.
- Solved customer challenges by offering relevant products and services.
- Answered customer questions about sizing, accessories, and merchandise care.

Crew Member Team Leader | Taco John's - Independence, MO

02/2016 - 10/2017

- Reviewed project requirements with customer to clarify issues and facilitate timely completion of job.
- Set performance goals for individual team members and created reward systems and contests.
- Supervised team members and oversaw effective and efficient completion of job duties.
- Educated crew workers on quality standards throughout assembly process.

EDUCATION

University of Missouri - Kansas City - Kansas City, MO

Expected in 05/2024

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

- 3.3 GPA
- Active Member of The Honors Program
- Jumpstart Volunteer
- Awarded Chancellors Transfer Scholarship

Metropolitan Community College - Kansas City - Kansas City, MO

05/2022

Associate of Computer Science

- 3.6 GPA
- Dean's List 4/6 Semesters
- Associate in Computer Science Awarded with Honors